Noah Zeilmann

Software Engineer

I am a proactive problem-solver with a passion for innovation. With over seven years in web development, I've honed my ability to adapt and lead effectively. I'm eager to join an Agile environment to evolve my skills and contribute to the team.



zeilmannnoah@gmail.com



+1 (816) 423-3521



Kansas City, United States



noahzeilmann.dev

SKILLS

Node JS

CI/CD

CSS

Redux Ruby on Rails

Postgresql

MSSOL

LANGUAGES

JavaScript



C#



Rubv







WORK EXPERIENCE

UI Engineer

Balance Innovations, A Brink's Division

Cash management software developed for the retail environment

- Lenexa, KS
- Completed initiatives to develop modern React websites in a Next.js environment to replace legacy software.
- Peer review code and create and maintain issues across a Kanban board.
- Queried and mutated data from our GraphQL API using the Apollo framework.

Contact: Kate Morr - KMorr@balanceinnovations.com

Application Developer

JE Dunn Construction

12/2020 - 11/2021

One of Missouri's top construction firms breaking ground and restoring buildings around the nation.

Kansas City, MO

- Created and maintained construction management and business internal utility applications in React paired with the web framework SPFX.
- Developed and peer reviewed .Net APIs for performing CRUD operations on construction management and internal business data.
- Led maintenance and development of our internal custom component library, developed with SPFX, React, and Storybook.JS.

Contact: Mark Stocks - Mark.Stocks@jedunn.com

Software Engineer

Cerner Corporation

06/2019 - 12/2020

Healthcare technology company, developing services, solutions, devices, and hardware for the healthcare industry.

- Developed medical coding software in Ruby on Rails, React, and SQL(Oracle and CCL) for use in multiple countries (Internationalized using React-INTL).
- Peer reviewed each others designs and written code using the Atlassian toolkit(Jira and Crucible).
- Supported and maintained existing projects using Jenkins CI & Splunk.

Contact: Binh Phung - Binh.Phung@cerner.com

Software Developer Intern

O'Reilly Auto Parts Corporate

10/2017 - 06/2019

Nationwide auto-parts supplier, providing auto-parts for both professional-service and do-it-yourself customers.

Springfield, MO

Kansas City, MO

- Worked closely with a team of fellow developers in a Lean-Agile environment using the Atlassian toolkit (Jira, Crucible, Confluence).
- Developed and maintained Java and Node JS web application and batch jobs for internal and external use.
- Created and used Postgres and DB2 databases to manage data.

Contact: Nicholas Jaross - nick.jaross@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BS in Software Development

Missouri State University

08/2015 - 05/2019 Springfield, MO

Minor in Web Application Development

Missouri State University

08/2017 - 05/2019 Springfield, MO